crispynuggets.com 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy

At CrispyNuggets.com we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate interests in improving our service by collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. The policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy.

## When does CrispyNuggets.com collect my personal information?

You may provide personal information to CrispyNuggets.com in one of three ways: (1) by sharing your e-mail when you provide submission tips to us or communicate with our employees, (2) by sharing your email or IM when you are using our content sharing features, and (3) by sharing your e-mail and other information when registering with CrispyNuggets.com, if required to do so in the future. We may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain access to our main public site.

In addition to personal information—such as name, street, e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers—we may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the operating system you are working on, the internet browser you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, and the web sites you visit directly before and after your visit to CrispyNuggets.com.

## How does CrispyNuggets.com use my personal information?

The more we know about you, the better we are able to customize our web site to suit your personal preferences and interests. The e-mail address you provide may be used by us for any reason, such as contacting you for editorial purposes, or advising you of any changes to our site. We may also from time to time send you messages about our marketing partners’ products. When you sign up for our updates, when available, or receive e-mail messages from CrispyNuggets.com, you will always be given the chance to opt-out of special offers and site updates. You may change your preferences at any time and will only be contacted in manners consistent with your stated preferences.

Non-personally identifiable information (such as stated above) may be shared in aggregate form with our advertisers or marketing partners but your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed to them.

## Is there anything else I should know about my privacy and CrispyNuggets.com?

Any information you disclose voluntarily through submissions, by commenting on a story, or by any forums which we may develop in the future, becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.
